Halid S. Macalangcom

Barrio B'laan, Brgy. Labangal,GSC | +639567817792 | vmhunterjob@gmail.com halidmacalangcom.vercel.app | linkedin.com/halid-macalangcom

Front-End Developer

Web developer with experience as a Digital Marketer Assistant for several online & local start-ups companies and with working knowledge of Wordpress and JavaScript frameworks. Transitioned into coding for the love of learning and to help contribute to applications that enrich lives and build communities

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, React, Vite, HTML, CSS, Wordpress(Divi Theme), Github, Gitlab, Graphic Design (Photoshop,Illustrator,Canva,), Well versed with MS office & Google Suite

Experience

Gensan Water District

General Santos, PHI

Internship

Apr 2019 - Jul 2019

Developed an attendance system with PHP & Bootstrap.

Adnovation Technologies

Sheridan, Wyoming, USA

Digital Marketing Assistant- Freelance

Aug 2020 - Nov 2022

- Design web banners & pop-up ads.
- Creating landing pages & traffic campaigns for the clients.

Ad Media Marketing Solutions

General Santos, PHI

Web Designer

Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

Developed an Ecommerce website with Wordpress.

ChatChatABC Philippines Inc.

Davao City, PHI

Junior Full-stack Developer

Nov 2022 - Jan 2023

 Handling a CRM system which involved troubleshooting technical issues, developing custom modules.

Academic Background

Holy Trinity College General Santos City

Certificate in Computer Science 2016-2020

Projects

Magic Memory Game - Course project by Shaun Pelling we developed a Simple memory game using react.js useEffects hooks and fetching data so how the game works it's mostly just a simple card memory game you just flip the card and find the similar icon/avatar and it's also had a turn counter for how many flip that you made.

https://github.com/vmhunter03/onepiececard (Github Repo)

Cooking Ninja - Still a project by Shaun Pelling on his course Build Web Apps with React & Firebase did create a CRUD project using React & Firebase so some of the basic that i learn on this how to properly use React Router, React Context & Reducer & basic of Firebase.

https://github.com/vmhunter03/cooking-ninja (Github Repo)